SHEME HAMITAJ



Contact

Address:

Tirana, Albania

Phone:

+355 68 46 833 47

Email:

shen.i@live.com

Website:

https://shemehamitaj.com

Languages

Albanian – Native
English – Excellent
Turkish – Excellent
Italian – Good

Skill Highlights

- Strategic planning
- Problem solving
- Quick learning
- Communication

Play Store Apps

 https://play.google.com/sto re/apps/dev?id=908394600 6672030470

Summary

Computer Engineer experienced in Web, Mobile & Desktop Apps, Robotics(ROS), Computer Vision, Embedded Systems. Programming languages include Javascript, Typescript, PHP, C, C++, Java, Python, C# etc. Currently working with Vue & NuxtJS and PHP & Laravel.

Experience

Ritech Solutions AG (Tirana, Albania)

Senior Software Developer: 09/2023 - Present

- Collaborating to design and implement software, ensuring seamless communication and code integration.
- Integrating APIs to enhance app functionality, focusing on user-friendly experiences.

circuly GmbH (Bielefeld, Germany)

Backend Lead Developer: 12/2022 – 08/2023

- Organizing work, prioritizing features and creating tasks.
- Planning and executing deployments to production.
- Gradual feature release via Unleash feature flags.

Full Stack Developer: 10/2021 - 12/2022

- Responsible for detailed feature planning and implementation on frontend and backend simultaneously.
- Payment processing via Adyen, Stripe, Braintree and Mollie.

Front End Developer: 01/2021 - 10/2021

- Writing clean, maintainable, and reusable code using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks such as Vue.js and NuxtJS.
- Writing automated tests using Jest and Cypress to ensure that the web application was functional and error-free.

Kocaeli University (Kocaeli, Turkey) **AMR Developer**: 08/2019 – 08/2020

 Work with a diverse team of electric and electronic engineers to create and develop AMR with SLAM & natural navigation.

Education

Bachelor of Science: **Computer Engineering** – Completed, 2020 **Kocaeli University**, Turkey

Scientific Papers

A Survey of ROS Security - 10/07/2019

IWW2019(10th International Conference on Image Processing, Wavelet and Applications)

Certificates & Awards

OBSS Code Master 2019 (hackathon) -19/12/2019

3rd Place at Kocaeli University

IELTS Academic – 14/07/2020 C1 Level : Score 7.5 out of 9.0